<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gymaholic</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">GYMAHOLIC</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">Technocrats.hicet@gmail.com-</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">ABS</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="diet">\nHere is a basic overview of the nutrients your body needs and what they do:\n
1) Proteins- The chemical building blocks from which our cells, organs, and
tissues are made.\n
2) Carbohydrates- Your basic energy source that is composed of simple and
complex carbohydrates.\n
3) Fats- These cells are your energy storage units.\n
4) Water- Essential for a number of vital bodily functions and accounts for
approximately 72% of your muscle tissue while transporting all of your
nutrients, increasing your blood volume, and eliminating waste.\n
5) Vitamins- These complex chemicals are required for bodily operations, are
produced naturally by the body, and are referred to as “organic compounds.\n
6) Minerals- Not produced in nature and of referred to as inorganic.\n
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
        Here is a more detailed description of the nutrients...\n
Proteins :\n
Q: Why Does The Body Need Protein?\n
A: Protein is a nutrient made up of amino acids. There are two types of amino acids.
Non-essential Amino Acids that can usually be synthesized by a healthy body from the
daily foods that we eat. Then there are Essential Amino Acids that must be obtained
through the daily diet.\n
Protein has a number of important roles in the body, including:\n
1.Repairing of body cells\n
2.Building and repairing muscles and bones\n
3.Providing a source of energy\n
4.Regulating many important metabolic processes in the body\n
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
Carbohydrates:\n
Q: Why does the body need carbohydrates?\n
A: The main reason your body needs carbohydrates is to provide energy. Carbohydrates
consist of starches (complex carbs) and sugars (simple carbs) that are broken down into
glucose, which then turns into energy.\n
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
Fats:\n
Q: I am trying to lose fat; do I need to incorporate fats into my diet?\n
A: Yes, fats are an important part of your body. They provide insulation and reserved
energy when you need it. Fat has also been found to raise energy levels and contributes to
your strength gains. When you short term energy supplies burn up (which can take 20-45
minutes), your fat cells are then used as the primary energy source.\n
owever, eating too much dietary fat may lead to the following health problems:\n
1.Obesity\n
2.Heart disease\n
3.Stroke\n
4.Hypertension\n
5.So you probably want to know which fats are the good fats and which fats are bad fats.\n
6.There are really three basic types of fat that include saturated fats, unsaturated fats, and
polysaturated fats.\n
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n

Saturated fats:\n
This kind of fat is like Crisco, its bad for you. It solidifies at room temperature and can
lead to a number of health problems. Saturated fats really have no role in our body. Foods
that contain the most saturated fat include:\n
1) High fat beef\n
2) Butter\n
3) Cheese\n
4) Chocolate\n
You are better off trying to avoid these foods.\n
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
Unsaturated fats:\n
These fats are better for you than saturated fats and are usually still liquid at room
temperature. Your body cannot manufacture these fats on its own but they still need to be
incorporated into your diet. They are found in olive oil, fish oil, and cold-water fish. Two
important unsaturated fats are polyunsaturated fats and Monosaturated fats.\n
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
Water:\n
Q: How much water should I be drinking everyday?\n
A: At least 2 glasses with each meal\n
If you want to look your best, water needs to be an essential part of your diet. It is
responsible for the transportation of vital nutrients and cleaning toxins from your blood.
Your body is made up of 40%-60% water. From constant perspiration and daily activity it is very easy to become dehydrated. Many of us never even know that we are close to
dehydration. When your throat becomes dry, your body is already dehydrated.\n
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
Nutrition Overview:\n
1. Fat loss and weight loss are dramatically accelerated when you “clean up” your
diet.\n
2.Proteins are the essential building blocks of muscle. Everyone needs protein in his
or her diet so that muscle is built and not lost.\n
3.Carbohydrates provide energy.\n
4.Saturated fats are unhealthy, whereas unsaturated, polysaturated, and
monosaturated fats are needed to burn off these saturated.\n
5.Drink water to help your body easily transport vital nutrients and to prevent the
possible effects of overtraining.\n
6.Vitamins and minerals help repair bodily tissue and promote the overall wellness
of the body.\n
        \nxxxxx-source bodybuilding.com-xxxxx

    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fragment">fragment</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="p_p">## Privacy Policy\n
        \n DextorAntony built the Gymaholic app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by DextorAntony at no cost and is intended for use as is.\nThis page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.\nIf you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.\nThe terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Gymaholic unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.\n
\n **Information Collection and Use**\n
        \nFor a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that I request will be retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way.
 \nLink to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app
        \n*   \n[Google Play Services](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)\n
       \n **Log Data**\n

\nI want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.\n
        \n**Security**\n
        \nI value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it.\n
        \n**Links to Other Sites**\n

\nThis Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me. Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.\n
    \n**Children’s Privacy**\n

\nThese Services do not address anyone under the age of 13\. I do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13\. In the case I discover that a child under 13 has provided me with personal information, I immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact me so that I will be able to do necessary actions.\n
       \n **Changes to This Privacy Policy**\n

\nI may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.\n

\n**Contact Us**\n

\nIf you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me.\n
    </string>
</resources>
