<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Gymaholic</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">GYMAHOLIC</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">noreply.dextor@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">YTube</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">List of Contents</string>
    <string name="diet">\nHere is a basic overview of the nutrients your body needs and what they do:\n
1) Proteins- The chemical building blocks from which our cells, organs, and
tissues are made.\n
2) Carbohydrates- Your basic energy source that is composed of simple and
complex carbohydrates.\n
3) Fats- These cells are your energy storage units.\n
4) Water- Essential for a number of vital bodily functions and accounts for
approximately 72% of your muscle tissue while transporting all of your
nutrients, increasing your blood volume, and eliminating waste.\n
5) Vitamins- These complex chemicals are required for bodily operations, are
produced naturally by the body, and are referred to as “organic compounds.\n
6) Minerals- Not produced in nature and of referred to as inorganic.\n
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
        Here is a more detailed description of the nutrients…\n
Proteins :\n
Q: Why Does The Body Need Protein?\n
A: Protein is a nutrient made up of amino acids. There are two types of amino acids.
Non-essential Amino Acids that can usually be synthesized by a healthy body from the
daily foods that we eat. Then there are Essential Amino Acids that must be obtained
through the daily diet.\n
Protein has a number of important roles in the body, including:\n
1.Repairing of body cells\n
2.Building and repairing muscles and bones\n
3.Providing a source of energy\n
4.Regulating many important metabolic processes in the body\n
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
Carbohydrates:\n
Q: Why does the body need carbohydrates?\n
A: The main reason your body needs carbohydrates is to provide energy. Carbohydrates
consist of starches (complex carbs) and sugars (simple carbs) that are broken down into
glucose, which then turns into energy.\n
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
Fats:\n
Q: I am trying to lose fat; do I need to incorporate fats into my diet?\n
A: Yes, fats are an important part of your body. They provide insulation and reserved
energy when you need it. Fat has also been found to raise energy levels and contributes to
your strength gains. When you short term energy supplies burn up (which can take 20-45
minutes), your fat cells are then used as the primary energy source.\n
owever, eating too much dietary fat may lead to the following health problems:\n
1.Obesity\n
2.Heart disease\n
3.Stroke\n
4.Hypertension\n
5.So you probably want to know which fats are the good fats and which fats are bad fats.\n
6.There are really three basic types of fat that include saturated fats, unsaturated fats, and
polysaturated fats.\n
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n

Saturated fats:\n
This kind of fat is like Crisco, its bad for you. It solidifies at room temperature and can
lead to a number of health problems. Saturated fats really have no role in our body. Foods
that contain the most saturated fat include:\n
1) High fat beef\n
2) Butter\n
3) Cheese\n
4) Chocolate\n
You are better off trying to avoid these foods.\n
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
Unsaturated fats:\n
These fats are better for you than saturated fats and are usually still liquid at room
temperature. Your body cannot manufacture these fats on its own but they still need to be
incorporated into your diet. They are found in olive oil, fish oil, and cold-water fish. Two
important unsaturated fats are polyunsaturated fats and Monosaturated fats.\n
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
Water:\n
Q: How much water should I be drinking everyday?\n
A: At least 2 glasses with each meal\n
If you want to look your best, water needs to be an essential part of your diet. It is
responsible for the transportation of vital nutrients and cleaning toxins from your blood.
Your body is made up of 40%-60% water. From constant perspiration and daily activity it is very easy to become dehydrated. Many of us never even know that we are close to
dehydration. When your throat becomes dry, your body is already dehydrated.\n
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
Nutrition Overview:\n
1. Fat loss and weight loss are dramatically accelerated when you “clean up” your
diet.\n
2.Proteins are the essential building blocks of muscle. Everyone needs protein in his
or her diet so that muscle is built and not lost.\n
3.Carbohydrates provide energy.\n
4.Saturated fats are unhealthy, whereas unsaturated, polysaturated, and
monosaturated fats are needed to burn off these saturated.\n
5.Drink water to help your body easily transport vital nutrients and to prevent the
possible effects of overtraining.\n
6.Vitamins and minerals help repair bodily tissue and promote the overall wellness
of the body.\n
        \nxxxxx-source bodybuilding.com-xxxxx

    </string>
    <string name="p_p">## Privacy Policy\n
        \n DextorAntony built the Gymaholic app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by DextorAntony at no cost and is intended for use as is.\nThis page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.\nIf you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.\nThe terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Gymaholic unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.\n
\n **Information Collection and Use**\n
        \nFor a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that I request will be retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way.
 \nLink to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app
        \n*   \n[Google Play Services](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)\n
       \n **Log Data**\n

\nI want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.\n
        \n**Security**\n
        \nI value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it.\n
        \n**Links to Other Sites**\n

\nThis Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me. Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.\n
    \n**Children’s Privacy**\n

\nThese Services do not address anyone under the age of 13\. I do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13\. In the case I discover that a child under 13 has provided me with personal information, I immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact me so that I will be able to do necessary actions.\n
       \n **Changes to This Privacy Policy**\n

\nI may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.\n

\n**Contact Us**\n

\nIf you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me.\n
    </string>
    <string name="ytube" tools:ignore="Typos">DISCLAIMER: I hereby declare that I do not own the rights to this video/vlog. All rights belong to the owner. No Copyright Infringement Intended. It has been under fair use act and i receive zer0 revenue and views since i use YouTube Data API V3 under GOOGLE privacy policy and Terms and conditions.No thermonuclear war, or Murder intended stab stab stab. \n
    \n#The Above Black screens indicates Youtube player.\n
    \n#After navigating to a certain page,wait until the youtube playback is completely loaded.\n
        \n#Click  the FullScreen icon on the player to go fullScreen mode.\n
        \n#Text is scrollable pull up or down to read and hold to copy.\n
    \n#Click on the YouTube icon to view a specific video and their channel on your external youtube app to subscribe and support them.\n
    \n#Click NEXT to continue.</string>
    <string name="page2">#Anabolic steroids, or anabolic-androgenic steroids (AAS), are the synthetic (made in a lab),When we lift weights heavier than what were used to, we create tiny microtears in muscle fibers. The body.s natural repair process repairs the tear and steroids boosts this process.
    \n#Anabolic steroids can be used as performance-enhancing drugs that increase muscle mass and decrease fat, as well as causing many undesirable effects. Some athletes, weightlifters and bodybuilders take them regularly to improve their physical performance and build up their bodies.\n
        \n#Hence it is highly recommended not to use any kind of steroids.\n
  </string>
    <string name="NXT">NEXT</string>
    <string name="plan">Here is what you need to know:\n

    1.Full body training is very effective at bringing up weak body parts because you can hit them first three times a week.
    \n2.While Arnold was known for split routines later in his training, he started his career on with full body workouts and still recommends it for new trainees.
    \n3.Bodybuilding legend Leroy Colbert was very adamant about full body training and said he never trained productively any other way.
    \n4.Vince Girondas full body routines used a novel progression. Instead of simply adding more weight to the bar, you reduce rest times.\n
\nFull body training is vastly underappreciated. Too bad, because it works exceptionally well.

\nConsider that, occasionally, life happens and there are times when you can only hit the gym two or three times a week. Those on five to six day splits often end up missing workouts because of work or family obligations. That kind of interruption in a split can mean that body parts may go a week or more without stimulation.

\nNot good. These kinds of scenarios are where full body workouts shine. But even if you are simply looking for a change of pace, they wont disappoint.



    </string>
    <string name="page3">Protein powder is a popular nutritional supplement. Protein is an essential macronutrient that helps build muscle, repair tissue, and make enzymes and hormones. Using protein powder may also aid weight loss and help people tone their muscles.
    \n1.Weight management
    \n2.Muscle growth
    \n3.Recovery after exercise
    \n4.Added nutrition</string>
    <string name="page4"> Don’t Train Maximally, Train Optimally\n
    \nWhen we train, we need to strive towards achieving our physical goals through optimal training, not maximal training. In other words, train smarter to accomplish your objective rather than training as hard as possible.
  Train smart. Train for your objective whether its physique, strength, flexibility, or something else and keep doing it to maintain what it is you wish to maintain.\n
        \nSleazy and antiquated fitness quotes like, “No pain no gain,” or “Excuses don’t burn calories,” or “Better sore than sorry” attract the masses via the many social media outlets that seek to place emphasis on aesthetics over function. But let it be known you can achieve proper function of the body AND beautiful aesthetics if you train optimally, not maximally.



    </string>
    <string name="page5">Diet and Weight Loss\n
    \nA healthy weight is an important element of good health. How much you eat and what you eat play central roles in maintaining a healthy weight or losing weight. Exercise is the other key actor.

    \nThe truth is, almost any diet will work if it helps you take in fewer calories. Diets do this in two main ways:

    \n1.Getting you to eat certain "good" foods and/or avoid "bad" ones
    \n2.Changing how you behave and the ways you think or feel about food\n
        \nThe best diet for losing weight is one that is good for all parts of your body, from your brain to your toes, and not just for your waistline. It is also one you can live with for a long time. In other words, a diet that offers plenty of good tasting and healthy choices, banishes few foods, and doesn\'t require an extensive and expensive list of groceries or supplements.



    </string>
    <string name="page6">When Is the Best Time to Exercise\n
    \nWhile some people are up at the crack of dawn to lace up their running shoes, others can not fathom a workout before noon.Finding the perfect time to exercise is as much about personal preference as it is physiology. Exercise is supposed to feel good
        \nPlenty of people tout the benefits of early morning sweat sessions, but if you can not fit in a workout before noon, dont sweat it. Research suggests the body could adapt to regular gym dates, so if we hit the weight room every day at 5 p.m., eventually we might perform better at that time than at any other time of day.




    </string>
    <string name="page7">Milk allergy: If you are allergic to cows milk, avoid using whey protein.\n
        \nWhey protein is the protein contained in whey, the watery portion of milk that separates from the curds when making cheese.Whey protein is commonly used for improving athletic performance and increasing strength, but evidence to support these uses is mixed. Whey protein is also used to reverse weight loss in people with HIV and to help prevent allergic conditions in infants.\n
    \nWhey protein is LIKELY SAFE for most children and adults when taken by mouth appropriately. High doses can cause some side effects such as increased bowel movements, nausea, thirst, bloating, cramps, reduced appetite, tiredness (fatigue), and headache.

    </string>
    <string name="page8">Mass gainers are protein too. Normally mass gainers supplies 22 to 35% of protein where as Protein powder as such supplies more than 60% proteins. Mass gainer contains more calories than regular whey protein. Mass gainer contains larger amounts of carbohydrates and fats to boost your calorie intake. Both are used for muscle recovery and muscle growth. Good mass gainers contain non sugar complex carbos for prolonged energy supply.\n
    \nIf someone is a hard gainer or someone who doesn\'t gain weight easily and want to build a significant amount of muscle mass, then mass gainer would be suitable for him. If one wants slow gains with controlled body fat percentage, a whey protein would probably be enough. Alternately, you can also use both mass gainer and whey protein to avoid gaining too much fat.</string>
    <string name="page9">\nRest is important, not just so you can catch your breath and be able to do more exercises, but also because it allows your muscles to recover. To get really scientific about this, we know that your muscles get energy for resistance training from a substance called creatine phosphate. After a set of exercises, it can take up to a minute for the levels of creatine phosphate to get back to normal. So, you gotta wait it out\n
    \nWe all have very different goals when it comes to working out, but for most people looking to improve their muscular fitness, its best to rest for 30 to 90 seconds between sets of an exercise. You should feel energized to get after your next set, but not so relaxed that your heart rate drops and your body cools down.</string>

    <string name="page10">When you are working out hard, you want to see results fast. While supplements such as whey protein and creatine have been proven to help improve strength, muscle growth and recovery, the amount of time it takes to work depends on a number of factors, including your workout routine, age and fitness level. Talk to your doctor before making changes to your exercise routine or adding supplements, such as whey and creatine, to your diet regimen.</string>
    <string name="thankyou">Hey Guys Thank you For Downloading Beta Version of this app,More contents with Improved UI/Ux designs using Google Flutter and Dart Programming Language  will be expected as an update at the end of November 2018</string>
    <string name="tf">Tamil Fitness</string>
    <string name="page12">Remember the two most important points:\n

    1.When training for strength, choose exercises that allow you to lift the most weight and require the most skill.\n
    2. When training for size, choose exercises that allow you to lift the most weight and offer the most isolation on the target area.\n
        \nThe other big point, which I hope you will remember and incorporate, is that you shouldn\'t focus exclusively on size until you have achieved at least "decent" strength in the major exercises.\n
        \nFinally, I will offer the standard reminder that none of these exercises will work for any goal if you dont manage the other elements of your training program volume, intensity, frequency as well as what you do outside the gym. Without proper food and supplements, good sleep habits, and sensible recovery between workouts, it doesn\'t matter which exercises you choose.
        That said, if you get everything else right, or mostly right, then matching your exercise selection to your goals could be the final piece of the puzzle.
</string>
    <string name="cts">Connect To Server</string>
    <string name="on">Server Online</string>
    <string name="page13">Meal Plan for Bulking and Maintaining:
    \n----4 Meals----
\n1.Breakfast
    \n2.Lunch
    \n3.Snack
    \n4.Dinner</string>
    <string name="p13">2000 Calories Food Plan</string>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="set_alarm">Set alarm</string>
    <string name="set_the_alarm_clock">Set the alarm clock!</string>
    <string name="unset_alarm">Unset alarm</string>
    <string name="videos_and_tips">Videos and Tips</string>
    <string name="developer_connect">Developer Connect</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="communicate">Communicate</string>
    <string name="motivational_quotes">Motivational Quotes</string>
    <string name="alarm">ALARM</string>
    <string name="nutrition">NUTRITION</string>
    <string name="full_body_workout_in_tamil">FULL BODY WORKOUT IN TAMIL</string>
    <string name="no_change_after_taking_protein_powder">No Change after Taking Protein Powder?</string>
    <string name="_5_exercises_for_size_and_strenght">5 Exercises For Size and Strength</string>
    <string name="do_steroids_build_muscle">DO STEROIDS BUILD MUSCLE ?</string>
    <string name="facts_of_protein_powder">Facts of Protein Powder</string>
    <string name="how_to_train_optimally">How To Train Optimally</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_and_diet_in_tamil">Weight loss and diet in Tamil</string>
    <string name="best_time_to_workout">Best time to Workout</string>
    <string name="side_effects_of_supplements">Side Effects Of supplements</string>
    <string name="whey_protein_vs_mass_gainer">Whey Protein Vs Mass Gainer</string>
    <string name="rest_time_between_sets">Rest Time Between Sets</string>
    <string name="shop">Shop Supplement</string>
</resources>
